[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Lily] Red Dragon is the head
of the biggest prostitution,
smuggling, white slavery,
kidnap-for-ransom,
and terrorist syndicate
in the Philippines.
That's why I can't understand
why she's coming after me.
[Helena] I need to utilize all my power
to be able to eliminate Emilia's enemies.
Prepare for war, Mercedes.
We will spare neither Julio nor Lily Cruz.
[Diego] That business is under
Mercedes Palacio's name.
If my hunch is right,
we'll find Red Dragon there.
[Lily] I will make sure I find her.
[Natalie] Whether you like it or not,
I'm your master and you are
my tempting and hot slave.
And I need to see you now.
[Madonna] You know,
if you're lucky enough,
you'll be one of the few
to see Red Dragon.
And if things work out,
you might get to meet her.
[Helena] Mercedes, keep an eye on Apollo.
Make sure that he does what's necessary
to improve the security detail
and income of this club.
Understood, madam.
[henchwoman 1] Is she the woman
Boss Apollo requested?
[henchwoman 2] What are you doing here?
You're not allowed here.
But I think it would be better
if I saw you without a mask.
Take him!
[suspenseful music playing]
[guns clatter]
[henchwomen and Diego grunting]
[grunting continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
[henchwoman 1] Boss!
Boss! There's trouble outside!
[Apollo] What?
[suspenseful music playing]
[henchwoman grunting]
[Lily] Diego?
Diego.
-What now?
-Let's go.
Red Dragon already left.
Let's get out of here.
[suspenseful music swells, stops]
Thank goodness nothing bad
happened to you.
Yes, Mom. Diego and I were careful.
We're safe and that's what matters.
It's just too bad that
we didn't see Red Dragon.
Lily!
You shouldn't have done that.
Do not go after Red Dragon on a whim!
I needed to do it, Uncle Damian.
I need to know who Red Dragon is
because she's been going after us.
If I don't make a move,
then all of us will be in danger.
What's important, Mom,
is that Diego and I are safe.
I know, Lily, but your uncle is right.
Don't go back there.
[tense music playing]
Even if I shouldn't, I have to.
The girls Red Dragon prostitutes
are minors.
I have to help those girls.
[tense music playing]
["La Vie En Rose" instrumental playing]
[birds chirping]
[young Julio] Flowers for you.
[young Helena] Thank you.
[young Julio]
I have something else for you.
It's a promise ring.
Helena, I love you.
I promise to marry you
and be with you forever.
["La Vie En Rose" instrumental playing]
No woman has ever toyed
with Julio Ardiente and not regretted it.
["La Vie En Rose" instrumental playing]
[objects clatter]
-[Madonna] Hi, sir!
-[upbeat electronic music plays]
-[Madonna] How was--I'm good!
-[man] How are you?
This is the police!
-Nobody move!
-[people shouting indistinctly]
[Madonna] Hey! Hey!
We're just working here!
[officer] Ma'am, ma'am,
sit down. Sit down.
[suspenseful music playing]
What's the meaning of this?
-It's a raid, sir.
-You got a warrant?
Yes, we do. Now, come with us.
[officer] Boys, take 'em away!
[suspenseful music playing]
[officer] Take them! Move! Move!
Go!
[indistinct shouting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[both squeal in fear]
Move! Move!
This is a raid! Nobody move!
-Move! Move! Move! Hurry! Move!
-[women crying, squealing]
-[officer 1] Move!
-[officer 2] Hurry! Go! Go!
-[officer 1] Move! Move!
-[officer 2] Go! Hurry!
[officer 3] Hands in the air!
Hands in the air!
-[officer 4] Hands in the air!
-[officer 3] The minors!
-[officer 2] The minors!
-[officer 4] Get the minors out!
-Get them!
-Come on, let's go!
Come with us. Hurry! Move!
-[officer 2] Move it!
-[officer 4] Hurry! Hurry!
[suspenseful music playing]
[women squealing]
[officer] We rescued all the female minors
locked in the club.
Thanks for the tip.
We were able to save them because of you.
Thank you, sir.
Please do everything you can
to return those girls
to their respective families.
By the way, were you able
to capture Red Dragon?
There was no sign of her, ma'am.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
The police raided Club Dragonfly.
They were able to shut it down,
arrest our staff,
and confiscate all our profits.
Tell our connections in the police
to make sure your name isn't
linked to the club in any way.
Copy, madam.
By the way, where's Apollo?
Escaped like a coward.
That idiot!
That man should be burned to ashes.
[exhales sharply] Mercedes…
Call our best man to hunt down Apollo.
What are you still doing there?!
Excuse me.
[exhales slowly]
Finally, Madrigal.
Do you like making me wait?
You're late!
[smooches]
But it's okay.
You made me miss you a little bit.
So, I'll punish you later.
What do you want from me now?
Wow! [laughs]
Don't act as if you don't like
our secret arrangement.
I have what you need,
and you have exactly what I want.
Aren't we the perfect match?
Hmm?
[Anna] Jepoy!
You witch!
-Anna!
-Get away from him, you flirt!
What are you doing here?!
I followed you to stop you
from seeing that woman!
Ooh…
[laughs]
-Go home!
-We have an angry guest.
Aren't you that little provincial girl
who's so scheming,
and who pretended to be Lily Cruz?
[Anna] Tell us the truth!
What do you want from my friend?!
-You'll just get him in trouble!
-Go home.
Go home.
Unless you're Madrigal's
girlfriend, guess what.
It's none of your business.
Natalie.
Talk to that little drama princess.
Your friend looks very jealous, Madrigal.
I'll leave you two to your drama.
[subtle tense music playing]
[car engine starts]
Anna. Wait. Anna, let's talk!
There's nothing to talk about, Jepoy.
It's pretty obvious
there's something going on
between you two.
You think I don't know her?
She's a criminal, Jepoy.
She'll get you in trouble!
Anna, I'm not doing anything wrong.
If that's true, then why did you
keep this from us?
Why hide it, Jepoy?
Because it's hard for me.
Even if I told you,
none of you would've believed me.
It hurts to admit
that I let Natalie use me.
Aren't we enough, Jepoy?
We're your friends. We trusted you, Jepoy.
Now, how can we trust you when
you're keeping secrets from us?
Do we still have your loyalty
or is it now with that woman?!
Anna, you are my family. You, Lily.
We're family.
What kind of question is that?
But how can we trust you now?
I'm sorry, Anna.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were my friend, Jepoy.
Friends don't keep secrets
from each other.
Anna. Anna, wait. Anna. Anna! Anna!
[dramatic music playing]
Why don't you just tell me straight up?
You're hiding something from me.
Are you talking to me, Papa?
[chuckling] We're the only ones here.
Please, drop the little act, Emilia.
I don't know what
you're talking about, Papa.
[deep sigh]
I can sense it, Emilia.
You can't hide anything from me.
I know you've met your mother.
[subtle tense music playing]
Huh? But my mother's dead!
Can you stop all this drama?
I am not talking about Esmeralda.
I am talking about your real mother!
So, it's true, Papa?!
My real mother's still alive?!
Is it true?!
Please, enough with your drama.
I've known for a long time
that you are aware that Esmeralda
was not your real mother!
How could you lie to me, Papa?
How could you do this to me?
So, that explains the awful way
you've been treating me.
I'm an illegitimate child!
I hate you, Papa! I super hate you!
[gloomy music playing]
She's been watching too many soap operas.
-[laughing]
-[suspenseful music playing]
Now, it's my time to play you, Papa.
-[suspenseful music intensifies]
-[chuckling]
Camia. Um… I'm sorry.
It's okay, Damian.
No, Camia. It isn't okay.
I shouldn't have raised my voice
at Lily the other day.
I'm just worried for her, that's all.
[sighs] I understand, Damian.
But I hope you'll try to know her better.
She takes after your brother.
She's fearless.
But we know what happened to my brother.
They killed him.
I don't want that to happen to Lily.
I don't want that to happen either.
But, Damian, there's no stopping Lily
from fulfilling her mission.
And as her mother, the best
I can do is give her advice,
and fight by her side.
I won't let Lily suffer
the same fate Dante did.
They'll have to kill me first
before they can kill her.
[cell phone vibrating]
I'm sorry, Camia.
I need to get back to work.
Take care of yourselves, okay?
[unsettling piano music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
Jaguar. It's so nice to see you.
[in distorted voice] You called
for me, Madam Red Dragon?
I have a mission for you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Find Apollo.
Are you questioning my order?
It's not like that, Madam Red Dragon.
But you have a lot of men.
You don't need my skills
to bring Apollo here.
What if I tell you…
it's your service that I want?
[suspenseful music playing]
[chuckles]
Very good, Jaguar! Very, very good!
[laughing]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[birds chirping]
[foreboding music playing]
[man 1] Let's get Arnaldo!
-[woman 1] Let's get Arnaldo!
-[man 1] Get him!
-Get him! Get him!
-There's Arnaldo!
[woman 3] He should be punished!
-[man 1] Get him!
-[woman 3] Punish him!
[man 1] Get him!
You'll never be a saint!
A leopard can never change its spots!
-[man 2] Punish him!
-[townspeople] Right! Yeah!
Punish the Ardientes!
[indistinct shouting]
[man 2] Punish the Ardientes!
Punish the Ardientes!
[indistinct shouting]
-Stop! Wait! Wait! Wait!
-[dramatic tense music playing]
Everyone, calm down.
Diego, don't you dare
protect that monster!
He has to pay for his family's
sins against us!
-That's right!
Hold on! Hold on!
Arnaldo's a changed man.
He's no longer the Arnaldo we all knew.
Let's give him a second chance.
-Never!
-Don't let him fool you!
We'll be no better than
criminals if we hurt others.
Violence isn't the solution.
Don't let your anger control you.
Arnaldo will own up to his mistakes
the legal way, through due process.
You can't tell us
how to feel about that monster!
[man 2] She's right!
We'll have our day, Arnaldo!
Remember that! Let's go!
[woman 5] Why is he protecting him?
I don't understand.
[townspeople talking indistinctly]
[woman 5] Why are you protecting him?
[man 2] Let's go!
[somber music playing]
Thank you. Thank you for protecting me.
Thank you.
Don't thank me just yet.
You may have changed,
but you can't run away
from the crimes you committed.
[sniffles]
Uh…
If what you say about me is true,
I'm ready to face the consequences.
I'll face them.
[sniffles]
All that I ask of you…
is to believe that anyone
can change. Even me.
-Thank you.
-[dramatic music playing]
[sniffles]
[foreboding music playing]
Madam, why-- why did you call for me?
Why were you hiding from me, Apollo?
I wasn't hiding from you, madam!
I just needed to lie low because
the cops were looking for me.
Liar.
You were hiding from me
because cops raided Club Dragonfly.
Thanks to your negligence!
[Apollo breathing heavily]
Give me another chance, madam.
I'm begging you. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
I'll do better next time.
Apollo, why don't we let
the gods decide on your fate?
[gloomy music playing]
Heads, you live. Tails, you die.
[suspenseful music playing]
What will it be, Apollo?
Are you ready, huh?
[spins coin]
[suspenseful music playing]
[laughs]
Madam, thank you so much.
I swear, I'll do a better job.
But, wait.
[suspenseful music playing]
Look.
Tails.
You die.
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Madam! Have mercy on me!
Madam! Have mercy…
Have mercy on me!
[suspenseful music playing]
[screaming]
Have mercy on me!
[screaming continues]
Look at Apollo.
That's what I want to do
to my new enemies.
-Because fire melts gold.
-[screaming continues]
I want to burn Lily Cruz alive!
[suspenseful music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[Damian] You have no idea
how vicious your enemies are.
But I'm here.
I will protect you from Red Dragon,
even if it kills me.
[tense music playing]
[engine starts]
[pensive music playing]
Mom.
Lily.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, dear.
I'm just thinking about your uncle.
Come on, Mom. Get some rest.
All right.
[Mercedes] Can we still trust Jaguar?
He might betray us because
our enemies are related to him.
No, I don't trust him at all.
Why don't we kill him?
Mercedes, sometimes, you're an idiot.
We still need to use Jaguar
against Lily Cruz.
For now, we'll let him do what he wants.
I'll tame that cat one day.
Oh, by the way, please call Governor Ruiz,
and tell him that it's time for me
to meet my allies as well as my enemies.
Right away. Excuse me.
[tense music playing]
Governor Ruiz.
Ms. Cruz. Thank you for coming.
Anything for the people of Ardiente.
And the people will definitely
benefit from this.
Let me introduce you to someone.
A philanthropist who wants
to help the townspeople.
I personally reached out
to her so she can help you.
She's the most successful
jeweler in the Philippines,
and she's willing to share her fortunes
with the people of Ardiente.
Oh, okay. Who is she?
Lily Cruz, meet Helena Montoya,
CEO of Montoya Industries.
[suspenseful music playing]
Lily Cruz, it's nice to meet you.
Ms. Cruz, we need to set
a meeting with you
and Mrs. Helena Montoya.
Who's Helena Montoya?
She's the CEO of Montoya Industries,
and she's interested in investing
in our luxury residences project
in the suburbs.
-Remember Helena Montoya?
-Yes.
The philanthropist who wants
to invest in our company.
But I want to review her proposal first.
[gloomy music playing]
Helena Montoya.
The same Helena Montoya who
wants to invest in my company.
That's me.
How come I didn't hear from you?
Oh, sorry.
I'm sure you've heard about
what happened to my properties.
That's why I'm more careful now.
I'm still studying your proposal.
I'm sorry to hear that, but no pressure.
I know there are more important
things to consider this time,
especially the well-being
of the people of Ardiente.
-Please.
-[chuckles]
[sinister music playing]
I'd like to thank you, Ms. Montoya,
for your willingness to help the people
of Poblacion Ardiente.
I was really moved
when Governor Ruiz told me
what the town has been through.
A place with so much promise
that's ravaged
by crime and corruption.
I know you want to help Ardiente.
So, let's work together.
Oh, yes, please. Yes.
Poblacion Ardiente needs people like you.
It's rare to find people
who truly want to help.
So, what are you proposing?
I'm going to have a charity event
to kick-start Oplan Restore
Poblacion Ardiente.
And I want you to spread the news.
Just tell everyone.
Your friends, your neighbors,
your relatives.
Let's help each other.
Together, we can help the people
of Ardiente rise from the ashes.
[tense music playing]
I've read through
all of Helena Montoya's files.
I didn't find any dirt on her.
She has also helped other provinces too.
Mom, I still don't trust her.
Do you think you can fool Lily Cruz?
Why, yes. Of course.
But it's not going to be easy.
The Ardientes have hardened her heart.
It'll be harder to pierce.
But if there's anyone
who could crush Lily Cruz,
that's me.
I know exactly what she's doing.
[suspenseful music playing]
Ms. Prianka told me about people like her.
Demons dressed as angels
have the darkest souls.
That's why I'll never trust that woman.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Mercedes] So, what's going
to be our next move?
Who goes first?
Julio or Lily Cruz?
As much as I hate Julio, he has resources,
and can still be of use to us.
Pack your bags, Mercedes.
It's time for me
to meet the devil himself.
[suspenseful music playing]
WELCOME TO POBLACION ARDIENTE
Welcome to Poblacion Ardiente.
My new home.
[suspenseful music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
[Jose exhales sharply]
Sir…
You have a visitor.
[gloomy tense music playing]
Governor Ruiz!
Here's my proposal for the charity event.
I hope it reaches Ms. Montoya.
[Emilia] Hmm…
I'm sure you and Helena Montoya
have already met.
[tense music playing]
You know, I wouldn't be surprised because…
you're like a leech.
You really enjoy sucking
other people's wealth.
[chuckles] That poor woman.
All she wanted was to help
but you've got other plans.
To exploit her.
I have no interest
in Helena Montoya's wealth
because I don't need it.
But you, though? You know, Governor Ruiz,
I'm here because I want to make sure
that Helena Montoya's help
goes to our people,
and not to this joke right in front of me!
The Corruption Queen!
-[tense music playing]
-[laughs]
Yeah, right. I so know you.
From the time that you were Ivy Aguas,
and then now, Lily Cruz. [giggles]
I know what you're like.
You're so fond of clinging
to filthy rich people. [laughs]
Well, you know, what can you
expect from someone like you
who's a bloodsucker?
[laughing]
Anyway, good luck. Good luck. Good luck!
Hey! Watch it!
-Sorry, ma'am.
-Get out of my way!
Who told you to stand there?!
-[chuckles]
-[tense music playing]
[Emilia] Open the gate!
[slow romantic music playing]
[suspenseful sting]
Hello, ex-lover.
Helena.
You came back.
Yes, I'm back. Well and alive.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Give us some privacy. Leave us!
[gloomy music playing]
[snaps fingers]
[tense music playing]
How have you been, Julio?
You're looking…
old.
And…
you smell it too.
The stench of death.
[laughing]
-What are you doing here?
-You know why I'm here.
You did terrible things to me, Julio.
You killed my father,
you took away my daughter,
and made me believe she was dead.
-Get over it.
-Get over it?! Just like that?!
You can no longer deprive me
of my right to be a mother.
You voided your right
to be a mother when you--
Cheated?! [laughs]
I didn't cheat on you, Julio.
You're just not man enough to admit it.
-Don't push my… buttons.
-[suspenseful sting]
[Helena] I'm not the same Helena
you used to belittle and trample on,
just like the other women in your life.
[gloomy tense music playing]
Have you heard…
of Red Dragon?
I am Red Dragon.
[suspenseful music playing]
I am powerful, stronger,
a survivor, a fighter.
And no man can put me down.
[suspenseful music playing]
[laughs] Is that fear
I see in your eyes, Julio?
Why don't you just admit it?
You're not in a position to brag.
Everybody in Ardiente hates you.
The people of this town detest you.
Your daughter's rebelling against you.
And your whole house is crumbling down.
The Ardiente family
is slowly breaking apart.
But don't worry.
There is a new sheriff in town,
and her name is Red Dragon.
[whispering] Until next time, ex-lover.
[tense music playing]
Alpha Mike Foxtrot!
It's all I can say. Darn!
[breathing sharply]
[tense music playing]
[dramatic tense music playing]
-[dramatic tense music playing]
-[objects clatter]
[music stops]
Mama? You wanted to talk to me?
Yes, Emilia.
The time has come for you
to know the whole truth.
[slow romantic music playing]
[young Julio] Once I achieve
my dream of becoming president,
you'll be my first lady.
Of course, Julio. I love you.
I love you too, Helena.
I'll ask my papa to support
your campaign for councilor.
This is the first step to our dreams.
Will Mr. Ramon say yes?
Julio, I'll do everything
to convince Papa.
I promise you. Our dreams will come true.
[Ramon] Helena, I won't support
Julio's campaign.
I trust Ponce more.
But, Papa, Julio promised
to help our business
once he's in power.
Look, Helena.
I'm running a delicate business.
And you're too young to understand this.
I need to be able to trust
every person in power.
If one of them proves to be the weak link
and gets intimidated by the police,
we'll all go down.
Papa, please. Just think it over.
Please.
-[Ramon] Enrique.
-Mr. Ramon.
Thanks for dropping by.
We've got a lot to discuss.
I know.
Rodolfo's in a bind again up north.
[scoffs, clicks tongue]
I've been thinking
that you should manage
our shipments there.
Of all my partners, you're the
only one who hasn't failed me.
Go on, Helena. Get some rest.
Enrique.
-[Enrique] Sir.
-[Ramon] Follow me.
[Enrique] Thank you
for accepting my invitation.
Although, I think your father
just made you do it.
[young Helena] Not really.
[laughs]
I knew it.
Your father wants me for you, doesn't he?
I don't know.
You're the only one who doesn't like me.
Truth is, I can get any woman,
but not you.
I'm sorry, Enrique.
But I'm in love with another man.
Julio Ardiente.
He's also the reason I accepted
your invitation, Enrique.
I wanted to discuss
Julio's campaign with you.
I hope you can convince Papa
to side with the Ardientes,
and support him.
Of all Papa's associates,
you're the only one he listens to.
Okay. I'll do it. But on one condition.
What?
[Enrique] You'll give me
a chance to love you.
-[suspenseful sting]
-[camera shutter clicks]
[muffled exclaim]
-What the hell?!
-[chuckles]
Get lost!
[gate squeaks open]
[suspenseful music playing]
Julio.
-Julio, wait.
-You tramp!
You cheated on me!
That's not true! It's not!
I just went with Enrique to convince him
to persuade Papa to support you!
Don't try to fool me!
No, Julio! Don't! Please!
I'm pregnant! We're going to have a baby.
That's why I'm helping you
reach your dreams.
We're going to have a family!
And yet, you're being a flirt!
No.
You have no right to that child!
You have no right to be a mother
or to be my wife!
[sobbing]
Julio, wait! Julio! Julio! Please! Julio!
-[screaming in pain]
-[doctor] Push. Push. Push.
Push. Push. Almost there.
-[grunting, screaming in pain]
-[doctor] Almost there.
The head's coming out.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screech]
Ramon.
Julio.
What are you doing here? What's going on?
[gunshot]
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
-Doc, how's my baby?
-[baby crying]
Doc? What are you doing?
Doc, where are you taking my baby?
[doctor] There's been a problem.
-But I promise, we will do everything…
-Doc, my baby!
-…to save your baby.
-Wait, that's my baby!
She's taking my baby!
Didn't you hear her?!
My baby! Doc! Doc!
Mr. Julio, here's your baby.
[dark tense music playing]
Emilia. I'll name you Emilia.
[young Helena] Doc.
I'm sorry, Helena.
Your baby developed some complications.
-Huh?
-She didn't make it.
[sobbing]
[young Helena] That can't be true, Doc!
-[doctor] I'm sorry.
-[young Helena] How?!
She was crying
when I gave birth to her, Doc!
-[dramatic music playing]
-[sobbing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[young Helena] I promise
to continue what you started, Papa.
I'll make your business grow,
and I will make it
the biggest in the country.
No one will dare to compete with us.
I swear
that one day, I'll avenge your death.
Ms. Helena, the guns
from China have arrived.
Let's go.
[gloomy music playing]
Now, do you see how evil your father is?
Mama.
[sobbing]
He killed my father and separated us.
The time has come for my revenge.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio] I've erased you from my life once.
And I can do it again, Helena.
Those who play with fire,
with Julio Ardiente, will burn!
[sinister music swelling]
[Camia] Lily, are you sure we're going
to that Helena Montoya's charity event?
[Lily] That's where I'll find out
whether she's my enemy or my ally.
I'm going to donate
20 million worth of diamonds
to the people of Ardiente.
[Raul] It won't reach the charity event
because we'll take all of it.
Only an idiot would betray Red Dragon.
[henchman] Someone's following us.
[gunfire]
I would like to introduce to you
my long-lost daughter,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
[applause]
[theme music playing]